<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CoMCoR</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CoMCoR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/page-copia-en-conflicto-de-daniel-redondo-2020-03-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page-copia-en-conflicto-de-daniel-redondo-2020-03-02/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The research will contribute to promote policy action aiming to reduce cancer survival disparities.
 Articles - Multimorbidity by Patient and Tumor Factors and Time-to-Surgery Among Colorectal Cancer Patients in Spain: A Population-Based Study. Miguel Angel Luque-Fernandez, Daniel Redondo-Sanchez, Shing Fung Lee, Miguel Rodríguez-Barranco, Mª Carmen Carmona-García, Rafael Marcos-Gragera, María José Sánchez.
Clinical Epidemiology
- Multimorbidity and short-term overall mortality among colorectal cancer patients in Spain: A population-based cohort study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/page/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/page/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Cancer recurrence and disease-free survival are usually analysed in clinical trials, enrolling healthier and younger patients than the general cancer population, thus being unrepresentative for the real-world where comorbid elderly patients are the group with higher cancer incidence rates.
As part of the effort to evaluate real-world comparative effectiveness research and cancer survival outcomes, the population-based cancer registries of Granada and Girona identified all incident cases (n=1,061) from colorectal cancer patients.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>